(Mrs Cooper:)For example, if Shelly was aboard,
he'd write "smart mouth" on his pigeon.
And then: Bam!
(Sheldon:)The Lord giveth
and the Lord bloweth away.
(Sheldon:)Well, Mom, according to my itinerary
for our weekend together...
(Sheldon:)- ...the fun begins with fried chicken.
- Sounds delicious.
Good, because I got you everything
you need to make it.
(Sheldon:)You are in for a treat.
(Sheldon:)My mother's fried chicken
is why we had to buy my dad...
(Sheldon:)...the extra large coffin.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, she just got off the plane.
She doesn't wanna cook.
(Sheldon:)Of course she does.
(Sheldon:)Making me food is her way of saying
"l love you."
Making me food when too tired...
(Sheldon:)...is her way of saying
"l really love you."
(Mrs Cooper:)I wouldn't mind going out
for a bite, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)Won't that spoil our appetites
for the chicken you're gonna make?
(Leonard:)All right.
We're going out. You like sushi?
There's a great place down the street.
(Mrs Cooper:)I've never had it, but there's no harm
in trying something new.
(Sheldon:)There's a lot of harm
(Sheldon:)That's why we test out drugs
and cosmetics on bunny rabbits.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, you're talking
Iike a crazy person.
(Mrs Cooper:)Actually, I had him tested as a child.
(Mrs Cooper:)Doctor says he's fine.
- Told you.
- I do regret not following up...
(Mrs Cooper:)...with that specialist in Houston.